h2owirelessnow.com 2019-06-22

# h2o Wireless Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY**  POLICY  
Effective February 2019  
This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how H20 Wireless, together with Locus Telecommunications, LLC (“H20”, “us”, “our”), collects, uses, and protects certain information that results from visiting our website or purchasing one of our products. H20 is committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy applies to the family of websites of H20, including the website of Locus Telecommunications, LLC (“Websites”).

**Collection of Personal Information  **  
H2O Wireless does not directly track any visitors who interact with our website(s), via cookies. H2O Wireless, therefore, does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.  
H2O collects personal information such as name, address, e-mail, telephone number, payment data, and service history. This personal information can be collected when you provide it to us such as when you make a purchase from us or call us for assistance with your account. For example, you may provide us a billing address and credit information, including your social security number, when signing up for service or perhaps purchasing a product through our SHOP, online store. H2O also collects anonymous demographic information that is not unique to you such as tracking information gathered as you navigate through the websites.

**_Automatically Collected Information:_**  We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit a Website, our systems automatically collect information such as your IP address and the type of browser you use. Similarly, all wireless communications systems know when your phone is turned on and approximately where the device is physically located; that's how calls or messages are delivered to you in real time.  
We use remarketing with Google AdWords. We and third party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the Double Click cookie) together to inform, optimize, and provide advertisements across the internet based on your past visits to our Websites. To remove yourself from our remarketing list, please clear your cache and cookies after you visit our Websites.  
**_Information from Other Sources:_**  We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with your account information. For example, we often receive information from the retailer from whom you purchased your H2O phone or device prior to initiating service with us. We also may use commercially available demographic and marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about products or services that we think will be of interest to you.

  **Use of Personal Information  **  
We use personal information for billing purposes, to provide services or complete transactions you have requested, to anticipate and resolve problems with your services, and tell you about products or services from H2O or others that we believe better meet your needs. More specifically, H2O may use e-mail, direct mail, and with your prior permission, wireless text messages, to inform you about products or services we think will interest you. You will have the option to unsubscribe or opt out of receiving these marketing or promotional communications, but you will continue to receive customer service-related and technical notifications, and other similar information via email, wireless text messages, or direct mail.   
H2O may offer the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways, or other similar promotions. Except as explained otherwise in the rules for a particular contest, giveaway, or promotion, any personal information you provide will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
Under federal law, you have a right, and we have a duty, to protect the confidentiality of information about your telephone usage, the services you buy from us, who you call, and the location of your device on our network when you make a voice call. This information is sometimes referred to as "Customer Proprietary Network Information," "CPNI," “Call Detail Record,” or “CDR.” We share CPNI and other personal information about you with H2O _a_ ffiliates, including Locus Telecommunications, LLC. Before sharing CPNI and/or CDR, we will first notify you of your rights under the law, describe how we intend to use the CPNI and/or CDR, and give you an opportunity to opt out of such usage (or, when required by law, to opt in).  
**Information Collected and Used by Third Parties**  
Our site includes links to third party websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don’t control. When you access a third party website from an H2O Website, purchase products or services not sold by H2O, or conduct other transactions with third parties, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of those third parties. The third party’s privacy practices may differ from ours. If you can’t find the privacy policy of any third party, you should contact that party directly for more information.

  **Email Addresses  **  
If you provide your email address, from time to time we may send you emails about new products and services, or promotional offers that we believe will interest you. We may also share your email address with marketing partners and/or providers of other products and services that you have indicated an interest in by opting in to receive such communications. Though we hope you’ll find this information useful, if you do not wish to receive such emails, please click on the "unsubscribe" link that we include in all of the emails we send. Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving commercial emails, we may still use your email address to answer any email inquiries you send us, to send messages about your account status, to alert you about technical issues, or to follow up on transactions or submissions of information that appear incomplete.

  **Information Disclosed to Third Parties**  
We disclose personal information to third parties, such as our third party payment provider, when it is necessary to complete a transaction you have requested or to initiate, render, bill, and collect for services. For example, our payment solution providers process your credit card transactions on our behalf. They can only use the personal information we give them to produce the billing statement.  
We will also disclose personal information if it is necessary to comply with law (e.g., court orders, subpoenas, E911 information, etc.), to enforce our subscriber agreements, to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our site, our customers, other carriers including our underlying carrier, the public or H2O, and to facilitate or verify the appropriate calculation of taxes, fees, or other obligations due to a local, state, or federal government.  
You may also want to use services and products offered by third party providers in conjunction with our wireless service. In those cases, you will be providing information to those third party providers, and information those third parties receive about you will be governed by their privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. For example, if you are roaming on the network of another carrier, information about your usage and the numbers you dial will be available to the carrier providing the service. And if you bought your wireless device from a third party retailer, both the retailer and H2O will have your personal information as a result of the transaction.  
H2O does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties.  
However, if H2O, one of its business units, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by another company, information about our customers and other visitors to this site would be among the transferred assets. 

  **Cookies**  
To help us tailor our site to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the web pages visited by placing a small entry in a text file, called a cookie, on your hard drive. The cookie contains an ID number that allows us to track the pages you’ve visited. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our site by making it more responsive to the needs of our users. Most browsers allow you to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don’t accept cookies, you won’t be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors.

  For more information about cookies, please visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>. You may opt out of the use of cookies at any time.

  **IP Addresses  **  
Your IP address is a number used to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. In addition to collecting your IP address, we also collect information such as the operating system on your computer and the web browser software you’re using to access our site so we can optimize our site for the most popular operating systems and web browsers. And, because we like to know how you found our site, we keep track of where you came from.

  **Banner Ads**  
H2O may use third-party advertising companies to place banner advertisements about our products and services on other websites. To measure advertising effectiveness and to offer selective ad content, the advertising companies may use an anonymous identifier to learn more about your visits to H2O Websites and other websites. This anonymous identifier is NOT your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or any other information that personally identifies you. The use of such anonymous identifiers (such as cookies, Web beacons or "tagging") is subject to the advertising company's privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. 

  **Security**  
The information we collect from our customers and visitors to our site is stored in databases we control. Physical access to the servers on which we store visitor information is restricted. We use your credit card information only to bill you for the products and services you order from us. We don’t share your credit card information with anyone, except as may be necessary to process your transactions. To protect the privacy of your credit card number and other ordering information, we encrypt this information for transit over the internet using a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connection. However, as effective as modern security practices are, no physical or electronic security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. Most web browsers allow use of an SSL connection. If your browser does not support use of an SSL connection, or if you prefer not to send your credit card number over the internet, you can place your order by calling us toll free at 1-800-643-4926. 

  **Additional Information for Individuals in the EU**  
While H2O is intended solely for personal use in the U.S. only, our privacy policy is aligned with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). If you are located in the European Union (“EU”), and access H20 Websites from the EU, you may have the right to: (1) request access or copies of personal data we process about you, (2) delete your personal data, unless an exception applies (i.e., the data is necessary to comply with an existing legal obligation), and/or (3) object to us processing your personal data in some circumstances (i.e., for direct marketing). Any persons located in the EU may contact customer service at [CustomerService@locus.net](mailto:CustomerService@locus.net) for any inquiries related to the any relevant GDPR protected information.

  **Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy is subject to change. If we need to change this Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we’ll post the revised policy promptly. By using h2owirelessnow.com, you agree that your visit to our site abides by the information contained in our Authorized Use Policy.

California customers: H2O does not disclose customers' personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, as governed by California Civil Code 1798.83.

  **Questions or Concerns**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [CustomerService@locus.net](mailto:CustomerService@locus.net).
